Guide to the Grover Lewis Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Published Work, 1955-2005
  - Avesta, "Musicians-1939," "Dirge for a Bird" - Published copy, Spring 1955 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Avesta, "You Always Wake Up" - Published copy and photocopy of selected pages, Fall 1955 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Avesta, "We Senile Sit" - Published copy and photocopy of selected pages, Spring 1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Avesta, "A Country Man on a Long Journey" - Published copy and photocopy of selected pages, Fall 1956 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Avesta, "Daddy is a Yellow Tie" - Published copy and photocopy of selected pages, Spring 1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Blues World, "Lookin' for Lightnin'" - Published copy, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cafésolo 9, "Lash LaRue in the Box Canyon" - Published copies, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - California, "On the Road with Ray: The First Bradbury Novel in 23 Years Takes Some Serendipitous Turns" - Related material, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - California, "On the Road with Ray: The First Bradbury Novel in 23 Years Takes Some Serendipitous Turns" - Typescripts and page proofs, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - California, "On the Road with Ray: The First Bradbury Novel in 23 Years Takes Some Serendipitous Turns" - Published copy and tear sheets, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Carolina Quarterly, "Daddy Is A Yellow Tie" - Published copy and tear sheets, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Coexistence Review, various poetry and short fiction (volumes 1 and 2) - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Coexistence Review, various poetry and short fiction (volumes 1 and 2) - Photocopies of Larry McMurtry's poetry, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Coexistence Review, various poetry and short fiction (volumes 1 and 2) - Photocopies of published copies (volumes 1 and 2), 1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cosmopolitan, "Paul Newman: Off Guard!" - Published copy, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dallas Times Herald, various book reviews - Newspaper clippings and photocopies, circa 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Desperado, "Lookin' for Lightnin'" - Published copy, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Desperado, "On the Road with Hank's Kid, 1978" - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Desperado, "On the Road with Hank's Kid, 1978" - Related material, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Desperado, "On the Road with Hank's Kid, 1978" - Errata sheet drafts, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Desperado, "On the Road with Hank's Kid, 1978" - Published copies and tear sheets, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Focus: Media, "Rolling Stone Speaks: Rock and Business—An Unstable but Possible Solution" - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Focus: Media, "Rolling Stone Speaks: Rock and Business—An Unstable but Possible Solution" - Related material, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Focus: Media, "Rolling Stone Speaks: Rock and Business—An Unstable but Possible Solution" - Promo material, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Focus: Media, "Rolling Stone Speaks: Rock and Business—An Unstable but Possible Solution" - Published copy and tear sheet, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fort Worth Star-Telegram, various book reviews, articles, and "Lookin' for Lightnin'" - Correspondence, circa 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Fort Worth Star-Telegram, various book reviews, articles, and "Lookin' for Lightnin'" - Newspaper clippings and photocopies, circa 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Government Lawlessness in America, "Prisoners of War in Sunny California" - Published copy, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Harbinger, "Notes on the Philosophy of Hip" - Photocopy (Winter 1961-1962) and published copy (Spring 1962) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Houston Chronicle, various book reviews and articles - Newspaper clippings and photocopies, circa 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Houston Post, various book reviews - Newspaper clipping, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - I'll Be There In The Morning If I Live - Related materials, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - I'll Be There In The Morning If I Live - Promotional material, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - I'll Be There In The Morning If I Live - Photocopy of typescript, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Inland, "A Country Man on a Long Day's Journey" - Tear sheet, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Janus, "Poem" - Published copy, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - L.A. Weekly, review of Suspectsby David Thomson - Handwritten notes and corrected typescripts, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - L.A. Weekly, review of Suspectsby David Thomson - Published copies and tear sheets, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - L.A. Weekly, "The Killing of Gus Hasford: The Rise and Fall of a Short-Timer" - Published copy, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Last Poem - Related material, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Last Poem - Published copies, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Latitudes, "The Wayward Bus" - Published material, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Times, various book reviews - Newspaper clippings and photocopies, circa 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "The Several Battles of Gustav Hasford" - Published copies, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Editorial correspondence, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Related material, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Research and handwritten notes, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Handwritten and typed notes, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Page proofs and typescript, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "True to the West" - Published copies, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Editorial correspondence, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Related material, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Research, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Audio-taped interview with Birney Imes, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Transcription of audio-taped interview with Birney Imes, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Handwritten and typed notes, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Typescripts and page proofs, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, "Juke Joints, Roadhouses, and Southern Parables" - Published copies, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Motive, "The Blues Project" - Published copies, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Movieline - General correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Movieline - Related material, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Movieline, review of Harlan Ellison's Harlan Ellison's Watching - Handwritten notes, September 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, review of Harlan Ellison's Harlan Ellison's Watching - Typescripts and page proofs, September 1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, review of Harlan Ellison's Harlan Ellison's Watching - Published copy and tear sheets, September 1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, review of Vincent Curio's Suicide Blonde: The Life of Gloria Grahame - Related material, October 1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Movieline, review of Vincent Curio's Suicide Blonde: The Life of Gloria Grahame - Handwritten and typed notes, October 1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Movieline, review of Vincent Curio's Suicide Blonde: The Life of Gloria Grahame - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, October 1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Movieline, review of Vincent Curio's Suicide Blonde: The Life of Gloria Grahame -Published copy and tear sheets, October 1989 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Movieline, review of Don Graham's No Name on the Bullet: A Biography of Audie Murphy - Related material, November 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Movieline, review of Don Graham's No Name on the Bullet: A Biography of Audie Murphy - Handwritten and typed notes, November 1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Movieline, review of Don Graham's No Name on the Bullet: A Biography of Audie Murphy - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, November 1989 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Movieline, review of Don Graham's No Name on the Bullet: A Biography of Audie Murphy - Published copy and tear sheets, November 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Movieline, review of Charles Kipps's Out of Focus: Power, Pride, and Prejudice—David Putnam in Hollywood - Related material, December 1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Movieline, review of Charles Kipps's Out of Focus: Power, Pride, and Prejudice—David Putnam in Hollywood - Handwritten and typed notes, December 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Movieline, review of Charles Kipps's Out of Focus: Power, Pride, and Prejudice—David Putnam in Hollywood - Research, December 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, review of Charles Kipps's Out of Focus: Power, Pride, and Prejudice—David Putnam in Hollywood - Typescripts and page proofs, December 1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Movieline, review of Charles Kipps's Out of Focus: Power, Pride, and Prejudice—David Putnam in Hollywood - Published copy and tear sheets, December 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, review of Barry Paris's Louise Brooks - Related material, January 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, review of Barry Paris's Louise Brooks - Research, January 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, review of Barry Paris's Louise Brooks - Handwritten notes, January 1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Movieline, review of Barry Paris's Louise Brooks - Typescript and page proofs, January 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Movieline, review of Barry Paris's Louise Brooks - Published copy and tear sheets, January 1990 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Movieline, review of Michael Godwin and Naomi Wise's On the Edge: The Life and Times of Francis Coppola - Related material, February 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Movieline, review of Michael Godwin and Naomi Wise's On the Edge: The Life and Times of Francis Coppola - Published copy and tear sheets, February 1990 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Movieline, review of David Thompson and Ian Christie's Scorsese on Scorsese - Related material, March 1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Movieline, review of David Thompson and Ian Christie's Scorsese on Scorsese - Handwritten and typed notes, March 1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Movieline, review of David Thompson and Ian Christie's Scorsese on Scorsese - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, March 1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Movieline, review of David Thompson and Ian Christie's Scorsese on Scorsese - Published copy and tear sheets, March 1990 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Movieline, review of Leonard J. Leff and Jerold L. Simmons's The Dame in the Kimono: Hollywood, Censorship and the Production Code From the 1920s to the 1960s - Related material, April 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Movieline, review of Leonard J. Leff and Jerold L. Simmons's The Dame in the Kimono: Hollywood, Censorship and the Production Code From the 1920s to the 1960s - Research, April 1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Movieline, review of Leonard J. Leff and Jerold L. Simmons's The Dame in the Kimono: Hollywood, Censorship and the Production Code From the 1920s to the 1960s - Handwritten and typed notes, April 1990 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Movieline, review of Leonard J. Leff and Jerold L. Simmons's The Dame in the Kimono: Hollywood, Censorship and the Production Code From the 1920s to the 1960s - Typescript and page proofs, April 1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Movieline, review of Leonard J. Leff and Jerold L. Simmons's The Dame in the Kimono: Hollywood, Censorship and the Production Code From the 1920s to the 1960s - Published copy and tear sheets, April 1990 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Movieline, review of Robert Giroux's A Deed of Death: The Story Behind the Unsolved Murder of Hollywood Director William Desmond Taylor - Related material, May 1990 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Movieline, review of Robert Giroux's A Deed of Death: The Story Behind the Unsolved Murder of Hollywood Director William Desmond Taylor - Handwritten and typed notes, May 1990 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Movieline, review of Robert Giroux's A Deed of Death: The Story Behind the Unsolved Murder of Hollywood Director William Desmond Taylor - Typescripts, May 1990 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Movieline, review of Robert Giroux's A Deed of Death: The Story Behind the Unsolved Murder of Hollywood Director William Desmond Taylor - Published copy and tear sheets, May 1990 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Movieline, review of Donald Spoto's Madcap: The Life of Preston Sturges - Related material, June 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, review of Donald Spoto's Madcap: The Life of Preston Sturges - Research, June 1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Movieline, review of Donald Spoto's Madcap: The Life of Preston Sturges - Handwritten and typed notes, June 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, review of Donald Spoto's Madcap: The Life of Preston Sturges - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, June 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, review of Donald Spoto's Madcap: The Life of Preston Sturges - Published copy and tear sheets, June 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Editorial correspondence, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Related material, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Research, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Handwritten and typed notes, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Corrected typescript and page proofs, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Movieline, review of Peter Bart's Fade Out: The Calamitous Final Days of MGM - Published copy and tear sheets, July 1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Editorial correspondence, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Related material, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Research, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Handwritten and typed notes, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Typescript and page proofs, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, review of Gavin Lambert's Norma Shearer: A Life - Published copy and tear sheets, August 1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Editorial correspondence, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Related materials, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Research, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Handwritten and typed notes, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Typescript and page proofs, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Movieline, review of Roger Corman andJim Jerome's How I Made A Hundred Movies in Hollywood and Never Lost a Dime - Published copy and tear sheets, September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Editorial correspondence, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Related material, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Research, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Handwritten and typed notes, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Typescript and page proofs, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Movieline, review of Bob Thomas's Clown Prince of Hollywood: The Antic Life and Times of Jack L. Warner - Published copy and tear sheets, October 1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Editorial correspondence, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Related material, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Research, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Handwritten and typed notes, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Typescript and page proofs, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Movieline, review of Steve Wick's Bad Company: Drugs, Hollywood, and the Cotton Club Murder - Published copy and tear sheets, November 1990 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Editorial correspondence, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Correspondence, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Related material, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Research, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Audio-taped interview with Aldo Ray, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Transcription of audio-taped interview with Aldo Ray, January 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6-10, Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Transcription of audio-taped interview with Aldo Ray - Handwritten and typed notes, January 1991 (Box 31, Folder 2-6)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Typescripts and page proofs, January 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7, Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Floppy disks with Aldo Ray article, January 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Movieline, "The Battle Cry of Aldo Ray" - Published copy and tear sheets, January 1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Movieline, review of Ronald Brownstein's The Power and the Glitter: The Hollywood-Washington Connection - Related material, April 1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Movieline, review of Ronald Brownstein's The Power and the Glitter: The Hollywood-Washington Connection - Research, April 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Movieline, review of Ronald Brownstein's The Power and the Glitter: The Hollywood-Washington Connection - Handwritten and typed notes, April 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Movieline, review of Ronald Brownstein's The Power and the Glitter: The Hollywood-Washington Connection - Typescriptsand page proofs, April 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Movieline, review of Ronald Brownstein's The Power and the Glitter: The Hollywood-Washington Connection - Published copy and tear sheets, April 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Movieline, review of David F. Friedman and Don De Nevi's A Youth in Babylon: Confessions of a Trash-Film King - Related materials, May 1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Movieline, review of David F. Friedman and Don De Nevi's A Youth in Babylon: Confessions of a Trash-Film King - Research, May 1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Movieline, review of David F. Friedman and Don De Nevi's A Youth in Babylon: Confessions of a Trash-Film King - Handwritten and typed notes, May 1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Movieline, review of David F. Friedman and Don De Nevi's A Youth in Babylon: Confessions of a Trash-Film King - Typescripts and page proofs, May 1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Movieline, review of David F. Friedman and Don De Nevi's A Youth in Babylon: Confessions of a Trash-Film King - Published copy and tear sheets, May 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Movieline, Peter Lefcourt's The Deal - Related materials, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Movieline, Peter Lefcourt's The Deal - Research, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Movieline, Peter Lefcourt's The Deal - Notes, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Movieline, Peter Lefcourt's The Deal - Typescripts and page proofs, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Movieline, Peter Lefcourt's The Deal - Published copy and tear sheets, June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - New West - Press passes, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - New West - Editorial correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - New West - General correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - New West - Inter-office correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - New West - New Westpromotional material, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - New West - Newspaper and magazine clippings and photocopies, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
  - New West - Various handwritten notes and related ephemera, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - New West - Various corrected typescripts, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - New West - Corrected page proofs for "Eureka" by John Gregory Dunne, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - New West - Corrected page proofs, newspaper clipping, and related material for "Hollywood With The Critics" by Jeanie Kasindorf, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - New West - Related material, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - New West, "Are You Ready For the Country or Will the Big City Do?" - Corrected typescript and page proofs, March 28, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - New West, "Are You Ready For the Country or Will the Big City Do?" - Related material, March 28, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - New West, "Are You Ready For the Country or Will the Big City Do?" - Tear sheets, March 28, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - New West, "K-K-Killing Time at Magic Mountain" - Corrected typescript, April 25, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - New West, "K-K-Killing Time at Magic Mountain" - Tear sheets, April 25, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - New West, "Totie Fields is Back on Her Foot Again" - Corrected typescript and page proofs, May 23, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - New West, "Totie Fields is Back on Her Foot Again" - Tear sheets, May 23, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - New West, "The Greening of ABC-TV" - Typed notes, June 20, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - New West, "The Greening of ABC-TV" - Corrected typescript and page proofs, June 20, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - New West, "The Greening of ABC-TV" - Corrected typescript and page proofs - Tear sheets, June 20, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - New West, "They Drive by Night but They Dance at Dawn" - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, July 18, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - New West, "They Drive by Night but They Dance at Dawn" - Tear sheets, July 18, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - New West, "Under the Stained Glass: The Reincarnation of Jimmy Webb" - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, October 10, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - New West, "Under the Stained Glass: The Reincarnation of Jimmy Webb" - Tear sheets, October 10, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)